Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Good evening everyone, I'm Eriko Hashimoto, AKB481's 17th term research student.
Today, the new AKB48 members will be announced.
I'm here at a filming location for the announcement of the new AKB48 members.
For those of you who watch YouTube
If you're watching e-verse, can you hear my voice?
Can you hear me?
Thank you very much.
Okay, so first up, we have our first announcement.
Here we go.
On September 27th, AKB486's second single will be released!
Today, we would like to announce the new members of the selected group from the shooting site of the music video.
There are 16 members selected!
We are in the middle of filming right now, but we would like to take a few moments out of the shoot to have them make an appearance.
The first member is here.Our first member is here. Come in.
I'm Ellie Chiba from Team A. Please.
I'll do my best.
Chiba-san, this is your fifth consecutive selection from Nemo Hamroomer. How do you feel now?
I'm very happy to be selected from Nemo Hamroomer for the fifth consecutive year. I'll do my best to make AKB48 more exciting.
Thank you very much for your support!
The first member selected for AKB48 62nd single was Erin Chiba.
Next, I would like to ask both of you to come here at the same time. Please go ahead!
Yes, I am Chiimi Mukai, aka Beauty of AKB48 Team A.
Yes, I am Yuki Kashiwagi aka Yukinashihiko from Team B.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
This is Yukinashi, who has been in AKB48 for 17 years.
I was surprised.
Congratulations.
And here is Ms. Chiimi Mukai, whose photo book is also doing very well.
Thank you.
She will be a stable selection.
Is it written?
It reads as written.
I am very happy to have been selected again,
I am very happy to be selected again, and with the momentum of the younger members, I feel a lot of gratitude to be selected,
I am very happy to be selected this time, and I feel grateful to be included in the group with the momentum of the younger members,
I will do my best for this single as well.
I would like to thank you in advance for your support.
I look forward to working with you.
Ei-chan, how old are you?
I am 17.
Really?
At birth.
I will do my best to show the breadth of my generation.
I look forward to working with you.
That's great.
The second and third selected members were Yuki Kashiwagi and Senmi Mukai.
Thank you.
All right.All right.
I, Yuki Chiba, would like to announce the next member.
The fourth member selected for the AKB4862 2nd single is Yuki Hashimoto.
Yay!
Thank you.
Thank you, Yuki.
Please tell us how it feels to be selected as the 8th member.
Yes, I am Yuki Hashimoto, an AKB4817 term research student.
I was really happy when I was selected,
Ever since I appeared on Countdown TV as an underdancer in the last album "I really love you", I had a strong desire to be selected,
Now that I have been selected, I would like to do my best to improve my performance and skills as a person. Thank you very much for your support.
I am very proud of you.
You did it!
Thank you very much.
Yes, Matchanko-chan. When did you see me?
I came in late June.
Is that when it happened?
Who would you like to inform first?
I called my mom that night and told her.
Was she happy?
Yes, she was very happy.
I'm glad. Congratulations.
How are you doing? I'm getting a lot of comments saying congratulations.
I'm getting a lot of congratulations.
They're suddenly appearing as the host.
It's going to be a boy.
Before the announcement.
Maybe the fans were wondering which one it was.
Well, it's a costume, isn't it?
The staff said that they were going to wear their own clothes.
This costume is for rugby or a rugger shirt.
Is it a rugby song? I'm not sure yet.
I'm not sure about that yet.
It's still just a costume.
I'm looking forward to it.Enjoy.
Next, here it is.
Please give us a message to your fans.
The reason I was selected for this year's contest is because of all the fans who have always supported me.
I think it is thanks to all the fans who always support me.
So, I will never forget to thank my fans in the future.
I will also never forget my original intention
I would like to continue my activities.
Thank you for all the support you have given to our fans.
I look forward to your continued support.
Firm.
Fun.
Eri, you love AKB.
I'm glad you made the cut.
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
She's cute.
Now I'd like to announce the next member.
Would you like to switch seats?
Not yet.
Not yet. Not yet.
The next member is here.
Not yet.
Still good.
Yes, I'm Maho Omori, a.k.a. Mahopion of AKB48 Team B.
Please.
Thank you.
She used to be a curry artist, so this will be her fourth consecutive selection.
How do you like it, Maho?
I'm so thrilled and excited every time, hoping that I'll be selected.
I'm very happy to be selected for the fourth time.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
Shall I sit down?
Oh, no, I failed.
No, thank you, thank you.No, thank you.
Thank you very much.
My eyes are a little bloodshot right now.
I'm sorry.
It's the end of the shoot.
My eyes are a little bloodshot.
It's been a long time.
I was exposed to a lot of Nick.
Yes, sir.
They keep saying rugby rugby rugby.
They even predict the title.
I think the title is "No Side of the Mind.
I'm going to say it without permission.
It's possible.
It's good.
That's good.
So we have announced up to 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 members.
Then I would like to go to the next member.
Here are the next members. Please go ahead.
Congratulations.
This is Kazuki Sorata, a third-year university student.
Two consecutive albums from your new group.
I really love you.
I really like you.
This is the second consecutive selection from the new group
Congratulations!
How do you feel?
Well, I'm very happy to have been selected for two consecutive albums.
I am also filled with gratitude for my fans, my family and the staff who have supported my abilities.
This single will be more matured than the previous one, and I hope to contribute to AKB48 as much as possible.
I will do my best to contribute to AKB48 as much as possible.
Thank you very much for your support.
You're so solid.
You look so confident.He's so regal.
He's cool.
To the next member.
Shall we go?
Let's have the next member come up.
Please go ahead.
Congratulations.
Yes, I am.
Yes, that's right.
Self introduction.
Well, I'm Miyu Shimo from Team 4.
Please take care of her.
Miyu is selected from Lipcross after a long time, and she will be tearing it up on her way home.
Yes.
Please tell us how you feel.
Well, first of all, I am really happy to be back,
But it is also thanks to all the fans who have supported me,
But when I was selected, the fans' words really helped me again and again,
I will do my best so that I can show you a more powerful me again.
I will do my best to show you a more powerful me again.
I am extremely happy.
I am really happy.
I will do my best.
Okay, then I would like to announce all three of us at the same time.
I'm so excited.
Here are the members. Go ahead!
Go to the front!
Why are you in the back?
I feel like I fell in goo goo when I see it.
Yes, I'm Rin Okabe from Team A.
I'm Yumina Oda from Team K.
Yes, I'm Nanami Kurano from Team 4.
Pleased to meet you.
It looks like a comic dialogue is about to start.It's like the start of a comic strip.
Please let us know how you feel about your fans.
Yes, I am very happy.
I'm very happy to see the younger members coming into the group,
I'm very happy to see that our junior members have joined us, and that one of our classmates is Hiiichan,
In the past, Yui Yui became the center of the group,
I am in the position of chasing after them, but I am also being chased by them,
I am in a position to chase after them, but I am also in a position to be chased by them,
So I have a sense of crisis, and I want to contribute to AKB,
I will do my best in this work as well.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, it's been a long time since I've been in a film, and since I'm an ex-boyfriend, this is my fourth film in a row, but...
Yes, I will continue to do my best, and since you chose me again, I will continue to do my best to make people in the world smile in my own way.
I would like to make people in the world smile again, just as I do.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, I am very happy to have been selected for this year's contest as well as the last one.
I am also very happy that my partner, Tao, who I do YouTube with, made it,
Yes, I will continue to do my best as AKB January.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much.
They are ready for the center here.
Now, let's go to the 62nd single
Rof Suzuki.
I would like to appear at the center.
Please go ahead then.
Hello, I'm Yui Oguri from AKB48.
No, no.
Hi.
Yui Oguri will be the center for the 52nd single released in 2018
Teacher Teacher, released in 2018.
How do you like it?
Yes, it's good. Well, yes.
Well, as you just said, it was my first time to play the center role.
I was 16 years old at the time, but now I'm 21 years old and I'm very happy to be able to play the center role for the first time in 5 years.
Now that I am 21 years old, I am very happy to be entrusted with the center role for the first time in 5 years.Now that I am 21 years old, I am very happy to be entrusted with the center for the first time in 5 years.
I'm also very happy to be entrusted as the center for the first time in about 5 years.
The feeling of being the center of the group is so much better than when I was entrusted to be the center at the age of 16.
I've seen many of my seniors graduate, and I've been through many AKB situations with them.
My feelings towards the center and my feelings towards this group have changed a lot.
I hope to make the most of that and be able to play the role of the center this time. I will do my best.
When did you hear that you were chosen as the center?
Well, I don't remember when, but I heard from the president.
Mr. President. My first dad.
From the president?
I heard from the president.
Did you tell your family about it?
Well...
I told my mom and dad, but I haven't told my uncles and grandparents yet.
Is this how they will know?
Secretly... but, you know, at Late Night.
Oh, wait, your initials...
Initials?
My name...
If Grandma saw it, she'd notice.
Oh, my God!
I just spoiled it for grandma.
Okay, so, any last words to your fans?
Yes, I do.
I hope many people will listen to this song.
I'm sure you'll be very happy to hear it.
I can't really say anything about the song yet, but, you know, I'm looking forward to it.
I can't tell you what the song is about yet, but I hope you'll look forward to it.
Please look forward to it!
Thank you very much.
Well, this is where we say goodbye to those of you who have to take pictures.
Congratulations to all of you in the comments section!
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Best regards.
Pleased to meet you.
Shall we go then?
Yes, I will.
Thank you very much.
Okay, now, let's hear from the two of you,
Okay, can I read them now?
Then we will announce the next selected members.
Please go ahead, two members.
Congratulations.
Good evening. I am Hitomi Honda.
I'm Yui Murayama.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
Excuse me.
Please tell us how you're feeling right now.
Yes.
Right now?
I'm Yuri because I'm the center,
I was selected as a teacher for the first time as a center teacher,
I was selected as a teacher for the first time,
I am very honored to be able to support Yuiri this time as well,
I am very honored to be able to support Yuiri again.
I will do my best. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I am very happy to be selected again,
I was chosen as the center for the previous album,
I am very happy to pass the baton again to Yui, who has worked hard with me since we first joined the group.
I will do my best to support Yui as much as I can. I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you.
You too, Eriko.
Two shots, right?
Thank you very much.
One word.A few words.
I will do my best for the 62nd single, so please support me.
Thank you very much.
Cute.
I knew it.
I've been starting all along.
Also, we have two more members to be selected for the 62nd single.
I would like to announce one of them.
Please go ahead.
Excuse me.
Hello. My name is Mizuki Yamauchi, and I have been selected as a member of the 62nd single. I look forward to working with you.
Cute.
Now.
Tell us how you feel.
Yes, I do.
I am very happy to be selected as a member again,
I also want to do my best to make this single the most exciting ever as one of the selected members.
We have been shooting the video with all our might, and I can't wait for you all to see it.
I hope you all enjoy the film.
Thank you very much.
Oh, well, there is one more.
One more? Oh, you mean that.
What? One more.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
One more.
One more?
What? One more?
Two more?
Two more! Two more!
Two more.
Not quite.Not quite yet.
I'm afraid it's a little difficult for the two of us.
I might be able to make it.
I'll check it out.
Let's see what they have to say.
Let's see the comments.
I knew it.
For each and every one of them.
And they're all responding to each and every one of them.
They're really excited about it.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
Yes.
Yes, it is.
Ah!
Arousing.
Yes, I see.
Who is your guess?
There are a lot of guesses flying around.
Oh, wow.
Lots of people are coming.
How many people did you say have seen it?
We're at 16,000 right now.
Oh, wow!
Thank you very much.
Who's that?
What?
Milky.
There's a bit of a time difference.
Yeah, it's quite a time difference.
Oh! Here it comes!
It looks like they're here.
Ah!Oh!
I went in the wrong direction.
It went that way.
I'll leave you alone.
Who's that?
Here he comes!
Yes, I'm here.
And I'd like to announce another member.
Please!
Thank you very much.
You all look so beautiful.
Okay, then.
Please tell us how you feel now.
This is the third time for me to be selected, so I would like to make the most of the results of the last two selections,
I would like to use the results of the two selections to explain myself more.
I hope you will support me and I will continue to do my best so that I can become a core member of BKB48.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much.
I would like to announce one more person, but I couldn't make it in time, so I would like to make an announcement myself.
The 16th member of AKB48 62nd single is Momoko Onishi.
Momoko Onishi was selected as the 8th singer for Shoot Sign, and she has been selected for 5 consecutive singles since Memohomorooma.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Okay, now that the announcement of all the selections has been made, I will now turn the attention back to AKB486.
Now that everyone has been selected, let's take a look at the list of the 16 selected members for the AKB486 2nd single.
I'd like to show you the list of the 16 selected members.
Momoko Onishi, Maho Omori.
Rin Okabe, Ms. Oggy. Erina Oda.
Yuuki Kashiwagi, Narumi Kurano, Airi Sato, Mie Shimoo.
Eri Chiba, Eriko Hashimoto, Hitomi Honda, Miyan Meikaichi, Ieiri Murayama, Mizuki Yamauchi, Sora Yamazaki.
Next, I have another important announcement regarding the release of the single.
It has been decided that the individual handshake event will return starting with the 62nd single!
Yes, we'll talk about it online as before.
Bugs.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.I'm sorry.
I'm getting a little tired of all the bugs.
Excuse me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Natural heights.
It's a natural high.
We will resume face-to-face handshaking sessions as well as online storytelling sessions as in the past.
All events will be held at Makuhari Messe. The dates are Saturday, October 28 Saturday, October 29 Sunday, November 18 Saturday, January 19 Sunday, December 23 Saturday, December 24
Sunday, January 19Saturday, December 23Saturday, December 24
Sunday, December 24th.
And the reservation for the official store version, which is necessary to participate in the individual handshaking event, will start from 22:00 today!
The members will be shaking hands with gloves to prevent infection by the new coronavirus, but we hope you will be able to join us for the first handshake event in a while. We hope you will be able to join us for the first handshake in a while.
Finally, I have one more important announcement for all the fans. Here it is!
If you play this video after this, a new video will play.
When you play this video, a new video will play.
When you play this video, a new video will be played.
When this video is played, a new video will be played.
Playback of this video will cause a new video to be played.
Sheesh!
Yes, I got 60 servings!
We have decided to hold a 3-day concert at the Nippon Budokan from Friday, December 20 to Sunday, December 22.
I am so happy.
On October 20, we will be holding a concert at the Nippon Budokan,
AKB is a gathering of children, parents and parents alike, and everything in between! Special! The concert will be a hilarious look back at legendary scenes and events to be passed down from generation to generation.
Yuki Kashiwagi, who has been a member of AKB48 for 17 years, will also participate in the conference, offering a special look back at the history of AKB48 for fans of the group as well as newcomers.
On Saturday, October 21, we will hold a Request Hour featuring only the songs from the theater performances.
Please vote for your favorite performance songs.
Details of the songs and voting method will be announced later on the official website.
This is the first time for DTJON to release the second volume of limited edition of DTJON performance songs,
How about you, Yuri?
But I know she can't do it, even though my video was shown,
But I think it will be a fun project for her fans,
I hope that new fans will come home with a variety of songs.We hope that new fans will come away with a variety of new songs.
Please look forward to it.
On Sunday, October 22, the last day of the event, we will be holding a concert by the new organization.
Please come and watch AKB48 as we continue to work together as one.
Ticket pre-sale starts today at 10:00 p.m. and will be available until August 13.
Tickets will be on sale until August 13th, so please make sure to get yours in time.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, close it already.
Yes, to close.
Sorry, I did it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm going to close.
It is time to say goodbye.
Yes, today's announcement is about AKB486's second single, which will be released on September 27.
And it will be released.
And the individual handshake session will resume. The official store will start accepting reservations for the official store version at 10:00 p.m. today.
In addition, a three-day concert will be held at the Nippon Budokan from Friday, October 20 to Sunday, October 22.
Tickets will be available for purchase starting at 10:00 p.m. today.
Finally, I would like to reiterate that this is the 62nd single, the center.
The 62nd?
Yui Oguri, please give a message to your fans.
Yes, I hope that the 62nd single will be one of the songs that will let people know how good AKB48 is now,
From now on, the group will be under a new structure with the team system suspended,
The group will be under a new structure now that the team system has been suspended, but the members of AKB48 will work together as one and do our best.
Please look forward to the 62nd single. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your time today.
So, good-bye. Bye-bye.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching